Guide to the Sigma Gamma Rho, Lambda Omicron Chapter records, 1994-2008
Sigma Gamma Rho, Lambda Omicron Chapter records
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Sigma Gamma Rho, Lambda Omicron Chapter records, 1994-2008
37-4-3712
Sigma Gamma Rho.Lambda Omicron Chapter.
1.1 cubic ft.
Correspondence, Manuscripts, Photographs, Printed Materials, Publications, Scrapbooks.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Records include correspondence, meeting minutes, scrapbooks, membership lists, notes pertaining to induction ceremonies, printed and mimeographed material, photographs, awards, and other items pertaining to Sigma Gamma Rho.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Records include correspondence, meeting minutes, scrapbooks, membership lists, notes pertaining to induction ceremonies, printed and mimeographed material, photographs, awards, and other items pertaining to Sigma Gamma Rho.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Sigma Gamma Rho.; Cornell University--Societies, etc.; Cornell University--Students.
Subjects:
Greek letter societies.; Women college students.
Form and Genre Terms:
Photographs.; Scrapbooks.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Box 2 is restricted to members of the Lambda Omicron members of Sigma Gamma Rho Sorority, who are on the updated list of chapter members found in the accession folder. They must show current photo ID.
CONTAINER LIST
- CD- "Black Greek Soundz", 2008 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Mwanamugium Essay Contest, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Tri-Chapter- Torch Binder, 2006-2008 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Meeting Agendas, Minutes, 2006-2007 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Meeting Agendas, Minutes, 2006-2007 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Meeting Notes, 2006-2007 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Event Flyers, 2006-2007 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Memos, Calendar, Correspondence, 2005-2006 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Memos, Calendar, Correspondence, 2005-2006 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Flyers, Mission Statement, 2005-2006 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Meeting Agendas, Minutes, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Meeting Agendas, Minutes, 1997-2004 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Awards, 2004-2008 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Newsletter- "The Northeast Collegian", Fall 2003, Jan 2005 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- History of Sigma Gamma Rho Society (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Providing Practical Recruitment Strategies for Undergraduate Chapters of the Northeast Region (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Northeast Region Area Rosters (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Office of Fraternity and Sorority Affairs, 2006-2007 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Restricted to Members Only (Box 2)
- Scrapbook, 2000-2004 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Scrapbook, 2000-2007 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Highest GPA Award plaque, Spring 2008 (Box 4)